A Guide to the Scheduling Office Records of Virginia Governor George F. Allen, 1993-1998
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Scheduling Office Records of Virginia Governor George F. Allen, 1993-1998
The Library of Virginia
35865
1 cu. ft. (1 box)
Virginia. Governor (1994-1998: Allen)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred by Georgia Root, Assistant Secretary of the Commonwealth, Richmond, Virginia, 22 June 1998.
Biographical Information
George Felix Allen was born March 8, 1952 in Whittier, California to famed NFL football coach George H. Allen and his wife Henrietta (Lumbroso) Allen. He graduated from the University of Virginia in 1971 and the University of Virginia School of Law in 1977. Allen served in the Virginia House of Delegates from 1982-1991 and served a short term in the U.S. House of Delegates in the early 1990s. In November 1993, Allen beat Attorney General Mary Sue Terry to become Governor. Governor Allen served until January 1998 and was succeeded by Governor James S. Gilmore. Governor Allen has been married to Susan (Brown) Allen since 1986 and they have three children, Forrest, Tyler, and Brooke. The family resides in Mount Vernon, Virginia.
Scope and Content
Contains the daily schedules of Governor George F. Allen and his wife, First Lady of Virginia, Susan Allen.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Governor George F. Allen's Schedules
Series II. First Lady Susan Allen's Schedules
Contents List
- Series I. Governor George F. Allen's Schedules, 1993-1998., Extent: 15 folders. (Box 1.)
  Contains schedules for Governor George F. Allen during the post-election/transition months, as well as during his tenure as Govenor of Virginia. Daily schedules include appointments, public appearances, departure and arrival times, and limited event details. Events listed in the schedules are mostly related to Allen's duties as Governor.
  Arranged chronologically.
  - 1993 November-December. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1994 January-February. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1994 March-April. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1994 May-June. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1994 July-October. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1994 November-1995 February. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1995 March-June. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1995 July-October. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1995 November-December. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 1996 January-April. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 1996 May-August. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 1996 September-December. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 1997 January-April. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 1997 May-August. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 1997 September-1998 January. (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Series II. First Lady, Susan Allen's Schedules, 1993-1998., Extent: 12 folders. (Box 1.)
  Contains schedules for First Lady of Virginia, Susan Allen during the post-election/transition months and during her husband's tenure as Governor of Virginia. Daily schedules include appointments, public appearances, departure and arrival times, and limited event details. Many of Mrs. Allen's events are related to the activities of the Allen children.
  - 1993 November-1994 April. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 1994 May-August. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 1994 September-December. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 1995 January-April. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 1995 May-August. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 1995 September-December. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 1996 January-April. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 1996 May-August. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 1996 September-December. (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - 1997 January-April. (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - 1997 May-August. (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - 1997 September-1998 January. (Box 1, Folder 27)